Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 6169 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials
1979- 1998
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees (NUHHCE)
Local 1199 Drug amd Hospital Union
6169 AV
31.78 cubic feet
30.7 linear ft.
Audiovisual material.
6694527
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 26, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 27, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5929: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Records 5929 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 5929 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia 5929 P: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Photographs 6069: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Additional Files 6084 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Women of Hope Poster Sets 6085 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project "Frederick Douglass and His Time" Posters 6089 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Posters 6140: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project 6140 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio Recordings 6169: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Files 6169 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia 6169 P: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Photographs
Labor unions -- Health facilities -- New York (State); Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Collective labor agreements -- Hospitals -- New York (State); Bread and Roses Cultural Project; National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees; National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union (New York, N.Y.)
6694527
- Las Manos del Hombre 22, 1 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  El de los 4 Cabos Blancos 23, Gena la de Blas 36, Desde Las Nubes 39, La Casa de un Amigo 41
- Beth Israel, 1994; 2 (Box 1)
  8/5/1994
- Treyillo, 3 (Box 1)
- El Poder del Jefe, 4 (Box 1)
- Beth Israel E.R. Footage, 5 (Box 1)
  various
- Murder She Wrote "Day of the Dead" clips, 1995; 6 (Box 1)
  9/18/1995
- Footage from "Fighting for Our Lives", 7 (Box 1)
- Murder She Wrote "Day of the Dead" selected clip, 1995; 8 (Box 1)
  10/20/1995
- 6169-14, 9 (Box 1)
- Latinas Prtt Exts. (Miriam Colon), 10 (Box 1)
- I am a child!, 11 (Box 1)
  An ILO film on child labour
- Mexico shoot, 12 (Box 1)
- Like a beautiful child, 1992; 13 (Box 1)
  11/25/1992
- Bread and Roses; Mark Levin, 14 (Box 1)
  Loftland Productions
- Universal Health Insurance, 1990; 15 (Box 1)
  CNN Headline News at 10:30 am.; June 10, 1990
- Bread and Roses "Invisible No More" - 6/23/1992, 16 (Box 1)
  MASTER; English w/Spanish subtitles
- Supreme Court (pt. 1 of 2) -- 4/26/1989, 17 (Box 1)
  Repro version - VHS-Beta Bump
- Voice of the people (Maloef); D.O.T. Hazmat, 18 (Box 1)
- Moynihan Office, 19 (Box 1)
  4/22
- Supreme Court - 7/6/1984 -- (pt. 2 of 2), 20 (Box 1)
  Repro version --
- Nasa Footage -- 6169-5, 21 (Box 1)
  (useless footage)
- 6169-19, 22 (Box 1)
- Awareness for Initial Response to Hazardous Materials Incidents, 23 (Box 1)
- Latinas Photos, 24 (Box 1)
  shot at WHYC
- Bread and Roses - Oral History - Group II Workshop (3/26/1979), 1 (Box 2)
  District 1199 -- Tape #2
- Patient Care Conference - Workshop II, 1979; 2 (Box 2)
  District 1199; Dec. 1, 1979 -- Tape #5
- Bread and Roses - Oral History Workshop at 1199, 1979; 3 (Box 2)
  March 7, 1979 -- Tape #2 -- Producer Marc Levin
- Bread and Roses - Brooklyn Jewish Federal Court House, 1979; 4 (Box 2)
  Brooklyn Jewish Bankruptcy Hearing - 10/15/1979
- Bread and Roses - Oral History Workshop, 1979; 5 (Box 2)
  Tape #4 -- at District 1199 -- March 7, 1979; Producer Marc Levin
- Bread and Roses - Take Care, 6 (Box 2)
  Tape #3-A
- Bread and Roses - Ozzie and Friends, 7 (Box 2)
  Interviews after performances
- Bread and Roses -- 1199 -- Brooklyn Jewish Pray In, 8 (Box 2)
  Tape #5
- Bread and Roses -- 1199 -- Ozzie Davis and Others, 1979; 9 (Box 2)
  5/18/1979 -- Stephanie Mills sings -- Tape #3
- Bread and Roses -- 1199, 10 (Box 2)
  Brooklyn Jewish Hospital Pray In; Sen. Javitts and Moynihan speak --- MASTER -- tape #2
- Bread and Roses -- 1199, 1979; 11 (Box 2)
  Women in Health Care a changing role -- 5/31/1979
- Bread and Roses -- 1199, 12 (Box 2)
  Brooklyn Jewish Prayer Vigil -- Tape #6
- Bread and Roses -- 1199, 13 (Box 2)
  Brooklyn Jewish Pray In -- Tape #4
- Bread and Roses -- 1199, 1979; 14 (Box 2)
  Brooklyn Jewish Pray In -- Oct. 12, 1979 -- Tape #1
- #3 Patient Care Conference, 1979; 15 (Box 2)
  12/1/1979 ---1199
- Patient Care Conference Workshop -- Dec. 1, 1979, 16 (Box 2)
  Tape #4 -- MASTER
- Bread and Roses -- District 1199, 1980; 17 (Box 2)
  Take Care -- Performed at Brookdale Hospital -- March 14, 1980
- 1199 Patient Care Conference -- 12/1/1979, 18 (Box 2)
- Bread and Roses -- Oral History, 1979; 19 (Box 2)
  Group II -- Workshop -- 3/26/1979 -- District 1199 -- Tape #1
- Bread and Roses -- Oral History Review at 1199, 1979; 20 (Box 2)
  Tape #1 -- March 7, 1979 -- Producer Marc Levin
- Bread and Roses -- Brooklyn Jewish Pray In, 21 (Box 2)
  Hand written notes
- Bread and Roses -- Long Island Jewish Memorial, 1979; 1 (Box 3)
  6/14/1979 --- CIJHMC
- Bread and Roses -- 1199 -- Long Island Jewish Memorial Hospital -- 6/14/1979, 2 (Box 3)
- Bread and Roses -- Jewish Memorial Hospital, 1979; 3 (Box 3)
  6/14/1979
- Brooklyn Memorial Jewish Hospital -- Bread and Roses, 1979; 4 (Box 3)
  9/25/1979
- Bread and Roses -- 1199 Demonstration at City Hall -- May 23, 1979, 5 (Box 3)
  Tape #3
- Bread and Roses -- 1199 Demonstration at City Hall -- May 25, 1979, 6 (Box 3)
  Tape #1
- Brooklyn Memorial Jewish Hospital, 7 (Box 3)
  1199 Bread and Roses -- Tape #2
- Bread and Roses -- 1199 Demonstration at City Hall -- May 23, 1979, 8 (Box 3)
  Tape #2
- Brooklyn Jewish Memorial Hospital, 1979; 9 (Box 3)
  Bread and Roses -- 1199 -- 6/25/1979
- Bread and Roses -- Long Island Jewish Memorial Hospital, 1979; 10 (Box 3)
- Bread and Roses -- Song -- Moe Foner interview, 11 (Box 3)
- Bread and Roses -- Brooklyn Jewish Hospital Victory, 12 (Box 3)
  Ossie and Ruby perform -- tape #2
- Bread and Roses -- Brooklyn Jewish Hospital Victory, 13 (Box 3)
  Shirley walks to work -- Ossie and Ruby perform -- tape #1
- Brooklyn Jewish Memorial Hospital -- Bread and Roses -- 1199, 1979; 14 (Box 3)
- Bread and Roses -- IJMC -- Long Island Jewish Hospital, 1979; 15 (Box 3)
- Bread and Roses -- 1199 -- Songs and inserts -- 10/3/1979, 16 (Box 3)
- Bread and Roses -- Moe Foner Interview at District 1199, 1979; 17 (Box 3)
  Oct. 3, 1979 -- tape #3
- Bread and Roses -- 1199 -- Long Island Jewish, 1979; 18 (Box 3)
  6/14/1979 -- tape #5
- Handwritten notes about the interviews, 1979; 19 (Box 3)
- The Fall and Rise of Local 1199, 1989; 1 (Box 4)
  Channel 2: the People; WCBS-TV/New York; December 30, 1989
- Health Care Rally, 1990; 2 (Box 4)
  News 13 at Noon; WNYT-TV/Albany; 6/13/1990 -- 10 Eyewitness News Tonight; WTEN-TV/Albany; 6/13/1990
- Health Care Rally, 1990; 3 (Box 4)
  Channel 2 News; WCBS-TV/New York; 6/13/1990 -- Eyewitness News; WABC-TV/New York; 6/13/1990
- Health Care Rally, 1990; 4 (Box 4)
  Inside Albany; WNET-TV New York; June 17, 1990
- Kings County Hospital Trauma Unit, 1990; 5 (Box 4)
  Eyewitness News; WABC-TV/New York; February 15, 1990
- Still Going Strong, 6 (Box 4)
  MASTER Edit
- 1199 RNS on the Front Line, 7 (Box 4)
  MASTER
- The 1199 Story, 8 (Box 4)
  3 minute video
- History of a fighting union: a bread and roses video, 9 (Box 4)
  produced by Moe Foner
- Take Care, 10 (Box 4)
  30 minutes -- color
- Still going strong: the Retired Members of Local 1199, 1992; 11 (Box 4)
  Bread & Roses Cultural Project, Inc.; 1992
- Behind the scenes with Julie Taymor; August 31, 1992, 12 (Box 4)
- Bread and Roses one hour documentary on 1199 Bread Roses Cultural Project, 1980; 13 (Box 4)
  Produced for PBS by Marc Levin (1980)
- Apollo Theatre - Old Skool to New, 1998; 14 (Box 4)
  Bread and Roses H.S. Video Class - (1998)
- Nows the time, 1996; 15 (Box 4)
  1199/League Employment, Training and Job Security Program (1996)
- Beth Abraham -- Bread and Roses - 1199 (9/26/1979), 1 (Box 5)
- Bread and Roses -- Sam Levinson (6/15/1979), 2 (Box 5)
- Bread and Roses -- Sam Levinson (6/15/1979), 3 (Box 5)
- Bread and Roses -- Group Discussion at Daughters of Jacob (Nov. 9, 1979), 4 (Box 5)
  tape #6
- Bread and Roses -- Pete Seeger Concert (Nov. 9, 1979), 5 (Box 5)
  tape #2
- Bread and Roses -- Pete Seeger Concert (Nov. 9, 1979), 6 (Box 5)
  tape #3
- Bread and Roses -- Group Discussion at Daughters of Jacob (No. 9, 1979), 7 (Box 5)
  tape #5
- Bread and Roses -- Health Care responsibility 1199 (5/31/1979), 8 (Box 5)
- Beth Abraham (9/26/1979), 9 (Box 5)
  Bread and Roses -- 1199
- Bread and Roses -- Patient Care Worker Interviews (Aug. 6, 1979), 10 (Box 5)
  tape #1
- Bread and Roses -- Patient Care -- Ida Berek - Interview in Bed, 11 (Box 5)
- Patient Care -- St. Lukes (9/22/1979), 12 (Box 5)
- Bread and Roses -- End of Ida Berek Int. (Nov. 9, 1979), 13 (Box 5)
  Beginning of Group Discussion at Daughters of Jacob
- Patient Care Worker Interviews -- Bread and Roses (8/6/1979), 14 (Box 5)
- St. Lukes -- Patient Care -- Patient Interviews, 15 (Box 5)
- Patient Care Workers Interview (Aug. 6, 1979) -- Bread and Roses, 16 (Box 5)
- Bread and Roses -- Brooklyn Jewish Press Conference at Governors Office (9/24/1979), 17 (Box 5)
- Bread and Roses -- Saving of Brooklyn Jewish Press Conference and Governors Office (Oct. 24, 1979), 18 (Box 5)
- Bread and Roses -- Brooklyn Jewish Pray In -, 19 (Box 5)
  1199 -- Sen. Moynihan -- tape #3
- Bread and Roses - Ozzie Davis and everybody (5/18/1979), 20 (Box 5)
  [Guy Davis] at 1199 -- tape #2
- Hand written notes about the tapes, 21 (Box 5)
- Brooklyn Memorial Jewish Hospital -- 1199 -- Bread and Roses, 1 (Box 6)
- Emergency Room -- 1199 -- Bread and Roses -- Brooklyn Jewish Hospital, 2 (Box 6)
- Bread and Roses -- Ozzie Davis and Son perform at 1199 (5/18/1979), 3 (Box 6)
- Bread and Roses -- Ozzie and Ruby (Oct. 3, 1979), 4 (Box 6)
- Bread and Roses -- Ozzie and Ruby at Columbia Presby, 5 (Box 6)
- Bread and Roses -- Ruby and Ozzie at Columbia Presby, 6 (Box 6)
- Bread and Roses -- Interview with Child Care Worker -- (5/7/1979, 7 (Box 6)
  Columbia Presbyterian
- Bread and Roses -- District 1199 (May 7, 1979), 8 (Box 6)
  Howard Roberts Choral -- Columbia Presbyterian
- Bread and Roses -- Brooklyn Jewish Victory (Nov. 2, 1979), 9 (Box 6)
  Ozzie and Ruby; Fred Richmond; Judge Costa
- Delegate Meeting -- Brooklyn Jewish Memorial Hospital (9/25/1979), 10 (Box 6)
  Bread and Roses
- Delegate Meeting -- Jewish Brooklyn Memorial Hospital (9/25/1979), 11 (Box 6)
  tape #1 -- 1199
- Bread and Roses -- 1199 -- Library Hakness Hall (5/8/1979), 12 (Box 6)
- Bread and Roses - District 1199 (May 7), 13 (Box 6)
  Howard Roberts Coral -- Columbia Presbyterian -- Tape #2
- Howard Robert Coral -- Bread and Roses -- 1199 (5/7/1979), 14 (Box 6)
- June 28 Retirees -- 1199 Schultz, 15 (Box 6)
- Bread and Roses -- Brooklyn Jewish Hospital Victory, 16 (Box 6)
  Leon Davis Speaks -- 1199 Plaza -- Noonie at Home
- Handwritten notes, 17 (Box 6)
- Bread and Roses Day - April 27th, 1980, 1 (Box 7)
  tape 1 -
- Hospital Strike 1959, 2 (Box 7)
- Kris Kross (6/16/1992), 3 (Box 7)
  1.Jump (Radio Edit); 2.Jump (Extended Mix)
- Metzger (From H-8), 4 (Box 7)
  reel 9
- Moe Foner Interview (Oct. 15, 1990), 5 (Box 7)
  reel 8 - (from H-8)
- Hilda, 6 (Box 7)
  R-10; (From H-8)
- Re-training; Carol Joyner/Debbie Temple, 7 (Box 7)
  Eric Shtob -- reel 7 (from H-8)
- 1199: the history of a fighting union, 8 (Box 7)
- Like it is: Black Union Leadership, 9 (Box 7)
  dub
- Still going strong: the retired members of Local 1199, 1991; 10 (Box 7)
  Sub-MASTER -- (12/19/1991)
- A family affair, 11 (Box 7)
- Health Care Reform: Why we need it 1199, 12 (Box 7)
  Sub-MASTER
- Now it's my time: 1199 Retirees Program, 13 (Box 7)
- Victory Memorial Hospital, 1992; 14 (Box 7)
  News 4, New York - WNBC-TV -- 11/5/1992; 11/6/1992; 11/9/1992; 11/10/1992
- Middletown Strike and Camp Vacamas, 1 (Box 8)
- Women of hope: Latinas Abriendo Camino, 2 (Box 8)
  (Spanish) -- MASTER
- Archivo de imagenes en movimiento; Las Manos del Hombre; Desde las Nubes; El de los Cabos Blancos, 3 (Box 8)
- American Agenda: Health Care, 1990; 4 (Box 8)
  World News Tonight -- ABC-TV/Network -- 4/30/1990; 5/1/1990; 5/2/1990; 5/3/1990
- Cam Vacamas and re-training - Arrival - kids, classroom, bread, gym, interview, 5 (Box 8)
- Re-training and graduation, 6 (Box 8)
- Re-training and kids graduation, 7 (Box 8)
- Kings County Trauma Unit, 1990; 8 (Box 8)
  Eyewitness News -- WABC-TV/New York -- 2/14/1990
- Re-training; Kids Interview; Adult Math Class; Adult Interviews; Kids Graduation, 9 (Box 8)
- Take Care 3, 1989; 10 (Box 8)
  Today - NBC-TV/Network -- 5/30/1989
- Re-training; Kids: Gym, Eating, Dance; Olivia Lynch Interview, 11 (Box 8)
- King: Montgomery to Memphis, 12 (Box 8)
  Pt.II of II - MASTER
- King: Montgomery to Memphis, 13 (Box 8)
  Pt. I of II - MASTER
- Aspiring Leaders, 1994; 14 (Box 8)
  aired 9/17/1994
- 1199 Religeous Meeting - Feb. 9, 1979, 1 (Box 9)
- Bread and Roses - District 1199, 1979; 2 (Box 9)
  UNICEP - Year of the Child Exhibit; tape #1 (Jan. 16, 1979) - Inserts of paintings, Media Works Crew -- Production - Marc Levin Camera - Di. McClinn; Director Emilio Marillio
- 1199 Religious Meeting (Feb. 9, 1979), 3 (Box 9)
- Bread and Roses (5/31/1979) - On patient care, 4 (Box 9)
  the Hospital Worker's responsibilities
- Bread and Roses - Oral History Group II Workshop, 1979; 5 (Box 9)
  District 1199 (3/26/1979) -- tape #3 - MASTER
- Bread and Roses - Sam Levinson at LIJ (Nov. 14, 1979), 6 (Box 9)
  TAPE #5 - MASTER
- Bread and Roses - Year of the Child Exhibit (Jan. 17, 1979) at 1199, 7 (Box 9)
  Gallery; Dance; Kids Group Int.; Marjorie Guthry -- crew- Media Works; Prod. Marc Levin -- MASTER
- Bread and Roses - Year of the Child Exhibit at District 1199 (Jan. 7, 1979), 8 (Box 9)
  tape #2 - Crew-Media Works; Production-Marc Levin - - MASTER
- Patient Care Conference - Workshop II (Dec. 1, 1979), 9 (Box 9)
  District 1199 -- Tape #5
- Bread and Roses - November 9, 1979 - Pete Seeger Concert - tape 1, 10 (Box 9)
- Bread and Roses - Year of the Child Exhibit - 1199 (Jan. 17, 1979), 11 (Box 9)
  tape #1 -- Crew-Media Works; Production-Marc Levin
- Bread and Roses - Year of the Child Exhibit, 1979; 12 (Box 9)
  tape #4 - Gene Young Interview (Jan. 17, 1979); District 1199 -- Crew-Media Works; Production-Marc Levin -- MASTER
- Bread and Roses - Oral History - Group II Workshop - District 1199 (3/26/1979), 13 (Box 9)
  tape #4 -- MASTER
- 1199 Patient Care (12/1/1979), 14 (Box 9)
  tape #1 -- MASTER
- Bread and Roses - Sam Levinson at LIJ (Nov. 14, 1979), 15 (Box 9)
- Sam Levinson - Bread and Roses -- LIJM, 16 (Box 9)
  tape #3 -- MASTER
- Sam Levinson - Bread and Roses - LIJM (11/14/1979), 17 (Box 9)
  tape #2 -- MASTER
- Sam Levinson - Bread and Roses - LIJM -- (11/19/1979), 18 (Box 9)
- Bread and Roses - 1199 -- Sam Levinson (6/15/1979), 19 (Box 9)
- Bread and Roses -- Sam Levinson -- 1199 (6/15/1979), 20 (Box 9)
- Handwritten notes on the films, 21 (Box 9)
- Motifore Hospital -- Bread and Roses -- 1199 (9/26/1979), 1 (Box 10)
  Beth Abrahams -- MASTER
- The Changing Role of Women in Health Care - Bread and Roses -- 1199 (5/31/1979), 2 (Box 10)
  MASTER -- tape #4
- Bread and roses - Oral History (3/7/1979), 3 (Box 10)
  MASTER -- tape #3
- Montefiore Hospital -- Bread and Roses -- 1199 (9/26/1979), 4 (Box 10)
  MASTER -- tape #2
- Bread and Roses -- Brooklyn Jewish Hospital, Emergency Room, 5 (Box 10)
  MASTER -- Tape #2
- Bread and Roses -- Montefiore Hospital (Sept. 18, 1980), 6 (Box 10)
- Bread and Roses -- Montifiore Hospital (Sept. 18, 1980), 7 (Box 10)
  Patient Care Conference - Speeches -- Tape #4
- Montifiore Hospital -- 1199 (9/26/1979), 8 (Box 10)
- Bread and Roses -- Labor Day Street Fair (Sept. 3, 1979), 9 (Box 10)
  MASTER -- Tape #3
- Bread and Roses -- Montifiore Hospital (Sept. 18), 10 (Box 10)
  Occupational Therapy - tape #1
- Bread and Roses -- Montifiore Hospital (Sept. 18, 1980), 11 (Box 10)
  Patient Care Conference - Cutaways and workshops
- Bread and Roses - Montifiore Hospital (Sept. 18, 1980), 12 (Box 10)
  Tape #2 -- Kitchen & interviews
- Montifiore Hospital -- Bread and Roses (9/26/1979), 13 (Box 10)
- 1199 Delegates Meeting (Oct. 3, 1979), 14 (Box 10)
- Montifiore Hospital -- Bread and Roses -- 1199 (9/26/1979), 15 (Box 10)
- Bread and Roses -- Montifiore Hospital (Sept. 18, 1980), 16 (Box 10)
  Patient Care Workshop -- tape #6 -- MASTER
- 1199 Meeting Statler Hilton -- Moe Foner, Tom Hayden -- Bread and Roses, 1979; 17 (Box 10)
  MASTER -- (10/3/1979)
- Bread and Roses -- Street Fair (9/3/1979), 18 (Box 10)
- 1199 Meeting - Jane Fonda Hilton -- Bread and Roses (10/3/1979), 19 (Box 10)
- 1199 Meeting Hilton -- Bread and Roses (10/3/1979), 20 (Box 10)
- Handwritten notes about the tapes, 21 (Box 10)
- 6169-190, 1 (Box 11)
- 6169-189, 2 (Box 11)
- 6169-188, 3 (Box 11)
- 6169-187, 4 (Box 11)
- 6169-183, 1995; 5 (Box 11)
  Univision (5/28/1995)
- 6169-186, 6 (Box 11)
- 6169-185, 7 (Box 11)
- 6169-184, 8 (Box 11)
- 6169-182, 9 (Box 11)
- 6169-181, 10 (Box 11)
- Apollo 11 - for all mankind -- 6169-180, 11 (Box 11)
- Copy of Latinas - Interacted MASTER Edit, 12 (Box 11)
- 6169-213, 1 (Box 12)
  Handwriting on tape is illegible
- 28A; 24A Duplicates; 32B, 2 (Box 12)
- 6169-215, 3 (Box 12)
- Facing AIDS: Stories of Healthcare Workers, 4 (Box 12)
- Hospital Strike 1959, 5 (Box 12)
- 6169-217, 6 (Box 12)
  Handwriting on label illegible
- 6169-221, 7 (Box 12)
  handwriting illegible on label
- 49-C -- 6169-220, 8 (Box 12)
- 6169-219, 9 (Box 12)
- Women of hope: Latinas Abriendo Camino, 10 (Box 12)
  Maria Peralta
- Notas Breves -- 42 C, 11 (Box 12)
- Latinas -- 6169-206, 12 (Box 12)
  handwriting on label is illegible
- Miniam Colon Segment, 13 (Box 12)
- EFX Test, 14 (Box 12)
- Latinas, 15 (Box 12)
  1.Opening and chapter title; 2.You bring out the Mexican in me
- Latinas, 16 (Box 12)
- Latinas, 17 (Box 12)
  Sound effects
- 6169-201, 18 (Box 12)
- 6169-202, 19 (Box 12)
- Dub of Latinas, 20 (Box 12)
- Latinas Segment, 21 (Box 12)
- Three Who Believed in Freedom, 22 (Box 12)
- Labor at the crossroads: still going strong, 1 (Box 13)
- A family affair: the 1990 Summer Institute, 2 (Box 13)
  1199 Training and Upgrading Fund
- City of Hope - Miriam Colon, 3 (Box 13)
- Bread and Roses, 1980; 4 (Box 13)
  One hour documentary on 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project -- Produced for PBS by Marc Levin @1980
- Fanlight Prod. -- Take Care, 5 (Box 13)
- Retired Member Video Documentary - 12/19/1991 - Still Going Strong, 6 (Box 13)
- Take Care, 7 (Box 13)
  Rough Cut Dub
- A Voice in your future: a personal message to the RNs of Washington from 1199NW, 8 (Box 13)
- 1199 RNS on the Front Line, 9 (Box 13)
- Keepers of the Dream: The History of Immigration and the Immigration Service, 10 (Box 13)
- Nursing Union: A production of the SEIU Nurse Alliance, 11 (Box 13)
- A Family Affair: the 1990 Summer Institute: 1199 Training and Upgrading Fund, 12 (Box 13)
- Hospital Strike: A Bread and Roses video, 13 (Box 13)
  1958 History - Produced by Moe Foner
- 1199 History, SEIU Convention 11/29/1990, 14 (Box 13)
- Practical Dreamer, 1987; 15 (Box 13)
  Dec. 21, 1987
- Mercy Hospital, 16 (Box 13)
- Health Care for all New York, 17 (Box 13)
- A Family Affair: the 1991 Summer Institute, 18 (Box 13)
  MASTER edit
- Julia Alvalez, 19 (Box 13)
- 1199 News Assembly, 20 (Box 13)
  Edited MASTER
- Health Care for All, 21 (Box 13)
- The 1199 Story, 22 (Box 13)
- Submitted by District 1199 Cultural Center, Inc., 23 (Box 13)
  TAKE CARE Lyricist: Micki Grant; Composer: Helen Miller (1980?)
- Sam Levinson: Excerpts from Bread and Roses, 24 (Box 13)
- Bread and Roses Day -- 5/9/1980, 25 (Box 13)
- District 1199's -- Lawrence 1912: the "Bread and Roses" Strike, 26 (Box 13)
  Bread and Roses Cultural Project--- film in a little canister
- Handwritten notes on media, 27 (Box 13)
- Health Care Industry Class -- 1199, 1 (Box 14)
  Edit MASTER
- Bread and Roses - TAKE CARE, 2 (Box 14)
  Tape 6-A
- Bread and Roses -- TAKE CARE, 3 (Box 14)
  tape 2-B
- Bread and Roses - District 1199 -- TAKE CARE of Brookdale, 4 (Box 14)
- Now its my time - Union 1199 Retirement Program, 5 (Box 14)
  MASTER Edit -- DO NOT ERASE --
- Bread and Roses -- TAKE CARE, 6 (Box 14)
  Tape 4-B -- MASTER
- Bread and Roses -- TAKE CARE, 7 (Box 14)
  Tape 2-A
- Bread and Roses -- TAKE CARE -- District 1199, 8 (Box 14)
  Tape 5-A
- Bread and Roses -- TAKE CARE, 9 (Box 14)
  Tape 6-B -- MASTER
- Bread and Roses -- TAKE CARE, 10 (Box 14)
  Tape 1-B -- MASTER
- Working American with Joan Mondale, 11 (Box 14)
  Plus New Patient Care -- MASTER
- Columbia Presp. -- (Oct. 3, 1979) -- Bread and Roses, 12 (Box 14)
  Ruby and Ozzie -- MASTER
- Bread and Roses -- 1199 -- Laundry Women Interview instead of Laura Job, 13 (Box 14)
  Sub Master -- 9 minute edit
- Bread and Roses -- Stanley Levinson Memorial, 14 (Box 14)
  Assembly Reel #1
- Bread and Roses -- 1199 -- Columbia Presbyterian audiences (5/7/1979), 15 (Box 14)
- Bread and Roses -- Pete Seeger Concert (Nov. 9, 1979), 16 (Box 14)
- Bread and Roses -- Excerpts, 17 (Box 14)
  New Edit MASTER
- Bread and Roses -- District 1199 -- Excerpts, 18 (Box 14)
  MASTER -- Producer Marc Levin
- Patient Care - Conferences -- District 1199, 19 (Box 14)
  MASTER --
- Bread and Roses -- Edited Excerpts, 20 (Box 14)
  pulled from the 1 hr. documentary
- Handwritten notes about the films, 21 (Box 14)
- Bus off to camp, 1 (Box 15)
- Soul II Soul, 2 (Box 15)
- Bread and Roses -- Produced by 1199, 3 (Box 15)
  Original MASTER --- DO NOT ERASE
- Moore - Interviewer, 4 (Box 15)
- Off to camp, 5 (Box 15)
- Apple Polishers - Channel 9 --- TAKE CARE, TAKE CARE, 6 (Box 15)
- Bread and Roses, 7 (Box 15)
- Moore Interview, 8 (Box 15)
- ABC-TV World News Tonight with Peter Jennings (1/20/1995), 9 (Box 15)
- Making a Difference, 10 (Box 15)
  1199 National Benefit Fund Summer Camp Program
- Latin Americans -- UCLA Archives, 11 (Box 15)
- Supreme Court - 4/26/1989, 12 (Box 15)
- Labor Research Association -- 1199 League Video -- Client Cut, 13 (Box 15)
- Latinas - Sinclair College, 14 (Box 15)
- Las Manos del Hombre 22; El de los 4 Cabos Blancos 23; Gena la de Blas 36; Desde Las Nubes 39; La Casa de un Amigo 41, 15 (Box 15)
- Hospital Workers Strike, 16 (Box 15)
- Bread and Roses Cultural Project, Inc. -- The Sensual Nature of Sound (Tania Leon Segment), 17 (Box 15)
- Ospria Promo, 18 (Box 15)
- Julie Swarey (8/31/1994), 19 (Box 15)
- Latinas - Helen Rodriguez (8/31/1994), 20 (Box 15)
- Latinas - 9/9/1994; Dolores Huerta, Pt. II, 21 (Box 15)
  also Part of Amelia Mesa Bains
- Latinas - 8/31/1994 -- Helen Rodriguez, 22 (Box 15)
  part II
- Latinas - 9/10/1994 -- Amalia Mesa, 23 (Box 15)
  part II -- tape 5
- Latinas - Autonia P (9/16/1994), 24 (Box 15)
  pt. II -- tape 9
- Miriam Colon Interview (Aug. 14, 1994), 25 (Box 15)
  Tape 1
- Latinas -- 10/17/1994; 11/4/1999, 26 (Box 15)
  Names on tape are illegible
- Latinas - 9/13/1994, 27 (Box 15)
  names on tape are illegible.
- Latinas - 8/31/1994, 28 (Box 15)
- Latinas, 29 (Box 15)
- Latinas -- 9/9/1997, 30 (Box 15)
- Latinas, 31 (Box 15)
- Mexican Shoot, 32 (Box 15)